If there is a god of cosplay...
I'm going to make her...
...smile upon me!
I'm not going down like this!
Not when I finally get it!
Do you see me, Kai-sama?
Look how cute I am now!
Everyone, look at me!
What's happening?
Seems our lovely Liliel has
lit a fire in miss Nagomi's heart.
He's right...
Her crowd just keeps growing!
B-but so is Liliel's!
It's not happening quite as fast,
but her crowd's getting bigger, too!
My Enchanted Armor
This really is incredible.
Eh?
You may not know this...
And Miss Liliel herself may not know this herself.
Many components contribute
to photographers forming a crowd:
the character's popularity, the cosplayer's fame,
skimpiness, but there's skill to it, too.
And if photographers stay in the crowd,
then the crowd will continue to grow, obviously.
Well, yeah, that is kinda obvious.
The trick, then, is to never let
a photographer want to leave!
You're still here?
You were here when she started.
Yeah, but like...
She just keeps them coming.
I don't know when to stop.
Look! Another good pose! She's so cute!
Miss Liliel's strength is her massive
inventory of poses and expressions!
It's hard to come up with poses on the fly.
Most newbies might have
five to ten poses in their repertoire.
But look at our Liliel...
I don't have enough time for everything!
Oh, right, I should do a pose from that one scene!
Gotta keep going. I've only got...
...a thousand more poses to do!
WHOOOOOAAA!
That's from that famous cover art!
Miss Liliel can faithfully reproduce
scenes from the manga and anime!
That's right!
And that means she doesn't need
to come up with poses on the fly.
Between the anime, the spinoff, and the manga,
there are tons of scenes to pick from.
And Ririsa has them all memorized!
This moment was a huge deal in the manga.
I want everyone to see this!
Whoa!
Amazing!
I was so focused on the Queens
I didn't notice she was here!
It just keeps going...
Miss Liliel has a unique skill...
The skill to keep photographers glued to their spot!
I may need to get some photos of my own!
Okay, I'm going in, too!
So many people are here to see my cosplay.
It's nerve-wracking.
And scary, too, with all the flashes going off.
But, I'm so happy.
I love this so much.
I've worked so hard on this.
Now I know it wasn't a waste!
Thank you, Nagomi-san.
You helped me realize something truly important.
You love Liliel, and cosplay is how you show that love.
Here's how I would respond now.
Cosplay might just be the way I show my love for Liliel.
I might only be cosplaying because of her.
But, that's okay.
I was a nerdy otaku who liked sexy outfits.
I always kept that to myself.
But cosplay gave me a place that accepted me,
where I felt safe.
It gave me the courage to be myself.
Which sounds weird,
because it lets me transform into someone else...
Cosplay is like my enchanted armor
that transforms me into my true self.
It's kinda nerdy, but that's how I'd put it.
That's the answer I would give you now, Nagomi-san!
I wrote you off as just another passionate newbie,
but I was wrong, Liliel.
You're the real deal.
Yet weirdly, I don't feel the usual anxiety.
Maybe it's 'cause I remembered how I felt starting off.
No...
I've never felt this comfortable
around another cosplayer.
There's something different about you.
Competing with Mayura was fun.
It got my blood pumping.
But...
Competing with you feels good, Liliel.
It feels like we shine brighter together.
I didn't think I could feel this way about a rival.
Wait. Did I just call you a rival?
Oh, whatever.
I'm sure we'll be rivals soon enough.
I heard there were two Queens here!
Nah, Mayura-sama left already.
What?! Then what's this crowd next to Nagomi's?
Some new girl!
This awesome newbie!
Who is she? What's going on?
I dunno, but who cares?
She's a really cute Liliel!
This is crazy, bro.
You only see this kinda excitement at Comiket.
Don't you need to get pictures of your client?
I gotta get pictures of the venue, too.
Damn, though...
People were hype about seeing Nagomi and Mayura,
but they're still just as hype for this girl.
I'm gonna make her famous!
I'm gonna make her go viral!
That Liliel cosplayer could be the next Queen.
I wish this moment could last forever...
But it can't.
I've got to be a professional.
This was a fantastic event.
Nagomi!
...Nagomi!
Thank you!
Sorry-
Nagomi-san.
Nagomi-san, I know you just said
you weren't acting like a real professional.
But...
THIS is the cosplayer I wanted
to work with so badly back then.
Nagomi-san...
Thanks.
Let's get back to the job.
Please...
You've already been working hard.
Cosplay Stream 55 will be closing soon.
Cosplayers, please head to the changing rooms.
Thank you, everyone!
Thank you, miss!
O-okay, I'm gonna go...
Wait, Liliel-chan!
Can I send you my pics?!
Do you have a card or socials?!
My eyes hurt and my makeup is dying!
If I stop to talk,
Liliel's gonna fall apart!
S-sorry!
She disappeared on us once again...
What is she, Cinderella?
Eh, it's okay.
It doesn't matter who she is, really.
She's left us with her glass slipper:
some great photos.
Damn, you're so cool, bro.
Don't I know it.
Nice job!
Senpai!
I got some great pics of you!
Li... Lili...
I'm so sorry!
Uh... you're good.
I'm so glad it went okay,
when I saw your face,
I felt so relieved...
But, but I just...
I-I'm so sorry! I'm really sorry!
Don't worry about what happened earlier.
Remember, in manga,
the protagonist always finds
their way out of trouble.
Today you were the main character of that story.
You were awesome out there, Ririsa!
Senpai...
Thank you... Thank you so much!
Guess my work here is done.
Can't believe I got to cosplay again...
Mayuri!
Eri?!
I-I didn't know you were here.
Mayuri!
DIVINE GUT BUSTER
Dash
You still always react by blocking low.
That dashing mid attack is so OP...
Why did you ghost everyone, idiot?!
Why didn't you say you were quitting?
Why didn't you say you were coming?!
Sorry. I didn't know what to say.
You moron!
You didn't need to throw it
all away like that, stupid!
Why do you keep calling me stupid?!
You were so nice to me on the phone!
Because we're friends, dummy!
Even if you stop cosplaying,
it's still the thing that brought us together!
All those experiences,
the good times, the friendship, too!
I didn't like Lustalotte! I liked you, Mayuri!
Cosplay might've been everything to you...
But don't throw away everything else, too!
Eri... I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
Don't apologize.
Then... Thank you?
No. Don't say anything.
Idiot.
You're so stupid.
Changing Room
H-hey, so...
HUFF HUFF HUFF
I can finally see the amazing details in your costume!
You look JUST like Icola-chan!
You're so cute!
DODODO
Whoa, is this embroidered?!
A-And I can see how goddamn adorable she is!
I've never seen this fabric at the store!
It's got some glitter to it, huh?
Dammit!
Why'd you pick her Chaos Form?
I love that version of her!
Really?!
She almost went evil trying to get strong,
but right when she was on the edge,
she came back in that new form, like,
it was such an emotional moment!
I know, right?!
Every week I was so worried about her!
But then she got super powerful and came back!
GRRRRR
OMG! Talking with her is fun.
But then she got super powerful and came back!
The relief after all that tension was crazy!
I hated her so much before, but...
But how can I?! She's a nerd like me!
Aw, man... I wish I could've gotten a picture of you!
I wanted to get a picture of you, too!
How's this?
Gimme your number, I'll text it to you.
O-okay! Yay, thanks!
Yeah. This feels right.
I love cosplayers. We're all in this together.
She and I are totally gonna be friends.
Hey, Liliel! Can I meet you by the entrance?
Yeah! Sorry, I'll go get changed!
K.... Ka, Kai...
Uh, hello.
Bow...
Is he your, uh... p-photographer?
Yup.
I TAKE THAT BACK
Oh, come on! Grow up, Nagomi!
You know what you have to do!
Hey! Do you wanna cosplay?
Huh?
I love new cosplayers!
We could do a Prince Charming group!
You could be Kai-sama!
Wha?!
So, uh, c-can I have your... Your number?
Women's Changing Room
Uh, s-sure?
YAY!
Feeling hot, huh? You got water?
Yes, I brought some!
She's a canteen girl.
Damn, that crowd you had was awesome!
You're definitely gonna be famous.
How'd it feel?
Oh, man, it was so much fun!
SHE'S SO PRECIOUS
Please stay this way forever!
Eh? No way!
Nagomi-san...
We only had our prep room booked till a certain time,
so we can't use it anymore...
I'm so sorry, but could you go
change in the public changing room?
It's all right.
I'm the one who messed up the schedule.
I don't mean to judge,
but Nagomi's really not that great of a coslpayer.
Ugh, that bitch. I just pretend I don't see her.
I love everyone...
But they don't feel the same.
I'll just get this over with.
I forgot someone helped me get into this...
And I can't reach the zipper!
Should I call Saito to help?
No, I can't have someone come
in here just to help me change,
that'd be so rude!
Stay calm.
Ignore the fact everyone's laughing at you.
Hey...
Do you need help?
Your cosplay is incredible!
I can't believe we get to talk to THE Nagomi-san!
Your Icola is so cute!
You were on this month's CosMedia, right?!
Right on the front cover! I had to get one!
I bought it, too!
Me too!
...Me too!
We love your work!
I thought everyone hated me...
I never though they'd...
That's right. I forgot.
I've been so focused on the horrible comments online.
I forgot that in real life,
no one has ever said anything mean to me.
They've all been nothing but nice to me.
Huh?
Nagomi-chan?!
I can't believe I lied all this time,
saying how much I loved every cosplayer.
How could I, when I never showed that love for myself?
And because I didn't like myself...
I saw everyone as a potential enemy.
I'm sorry, everyone. I'm sorry, Nagomi.
Sorry!
I'm just so relieved to be done, it all came out.
I'm totally fine!
I was worried for a sec!
Are you sure you're okay?
The pressure on pros must be crazy.
I get it.
Girl, you're not even a pro.
I love cosplayers!
Liliel!
Nagomi-san!
You'd better be at Summer Comiket.
I'll be there for work as the most
popular character of the summer.
Okay! I'll be there as Liliel!
Good.
Everyone's saying they want
to get pictures of you there.
Is this from earlier? Wait, 50K shares?!
Huh? Sorry, should I have asked first?
I already uploaded a bunch with you.
Don't know this cosplayer
but she's so freaking cute...!
Why are you surprised?
You saw the crowd around you.
Sooner or later, you're gonna be famous.
That pressure you're feeling is a rite of passage.
Try to enjoy it, yeah?
Don't worry.
If you ever forget the smile on your face today...
I'll return the favor and give
you the reminder you need.
Figures she's exhausted.
Between the crowd of photographers,
and what happened with Sensei and Nagomi...
I'm glad she had a good time.
They probably think we're some cutesy couple.
I'd freak out if she were Liliel,
but she's just Ririsa!
Where are we? Did we miss our stop?
We're good.
I'll keep an eye out. You go back to sleep.
I'll be there for you!
I'm so glad I have him. I don't have to worry.
Whew, it's warm in here.
Cold, so she moved to
a warmer train car
I know those two.
Senpai.
Senpai, I love you so much.
Promise you'll stay with me forever?
O-o-oh my god!
S-s-s-she's using the L word?!
O-Okumura! Hello?!
Yeah, I promise.
Wait, is that Sensei?
S-sorry, I didn't mean to eavesdrop...
I had no idea the two of you were so close.
We are! Especially after the great event
we had with Liliel today!
I'm so proud of her for how perfectly she can
show off her love for Liliel through cosplay!
Please, it's all thanks to your
tremendous support, Senpai!
You're the whole reason I can put
so much energy into cosplay!
See?!
You see?!
We make the best partners!
Oh, they meant something else.
Cosplayer and photographer, I guess.
Christ, though, do they see themselves?
See, this shot of Liliel came out so good!
It did! Great job, Senpai!
Are they sure they're not together?
Man, kids these days...
...I don't get 'em one bit.
Cosplay, you say?
I know how the world at
large might think of cosplay,
but they're putting their hearts into it.
And to do that,
they need a club room.
I'll be their advisor and keep them on track.
Well, this isn't solely my decision to make.
As for whether their activities meet the mark,
I'll let our wonderful student council have their say.
Yeah, sounds about right...
I'm more concerned about whether it's okay
to put this out for the other students to see.
Dude, look at her!
What do you think, Hanyuu-sensei?
Her tits are huge!
She's kept this a secret until now, right?
Couldn't this stir up some
ruckus amongst the students?
We're supposed to hear back about our report today...
Ririsa!
Mikari-chan?
What the hell is wrong with you?!
You're in big trouble! Just look at the blackboard!
What?
Five Rising Stars